

Holly Thomas

Full-Stack Web Developer



60% 50% 5%

CSS

JS

8%

HTML

C#



- Collaboration and teamwork
 - Empathy and understanding
- Passion and problem solving
- Giving and recieving Feedback
- Self-lead lerning and continuous improvement
 - Motivating and empowering others
 - Explaining complex ideas simply

About Me

I am experienced in media and design, particularly in the field of video, and have recently transitioned into software development.

I have excellent written and verbal communication skills, and value a collaborative culture of transparency and feedback. I enjoy problem solving, working around both technical and creative challenges to find interesting new solutions.

Work History



April 2018 - Present

Running my own company, developing concepts with clients, leading projects, managing client relationships.

Spotify IT & AV Engineer

May 2014 - April 2018

Administrator for Atlassian suite & Google administrator console, project manager for office & stage instalations, designed & project managed for building of internal systems.

University of Portsmouth AV Loan Store Technician

April 2018 - Present

Technical support, administering equipment database and booking systems, maintenance & training on camera equipment.

Education



The Code Institute

Full-Stack Software Developer



The University of Portsmouth BA Film